Greetings!
Welcome back.
Potato... Elavi!
You're printing taters!
That's illegal.
How's everybody?
Po-po-ap-twat.
I like it.
I'm microwaving potato as we speak.
Nice!
How many minutes?
Oh!
Atlas!
Your two-month anniversary!
The Martin.
Hey Oliver, glad you're feeling better.
I visited Copenhagen with class and visited the BioInnovation Institute and Dark Cosmology Center.
And King Bagels.
Or King... I don't know what that is.
Donut.
King Donut.
Crown jewels, maybe.
That's gotta be what that means.
Nice.
You actually visited Dark, huh?
Maybe I saw you.
I have a feeling today will be great.
You don't say RoboRa.
I think so too.
Man, I was sick at the start of this week.
Felt terrible.
I'm back on top now though.
So now we're gonna play some more Terraria.
Mhm.
Royal Bagel.
Ah!
Nice!
Oh, I get it now.
Of course.
Gotcha.
Ran out of space in the message.
I see.
Well, I hope you enjoyed it.
Alejandro!
First time I actually catch the stream live.
I hope you're doing better, Oliver.
I'm doing great, yeah.
A lot of work though these days.
Lots of stuff to do.
But I am cramming and gaming whenever I can.
So that's the beautiful part of that.
Oliver has a balloon and a mask.
And I've been playing for almost 30 hours.
How about that?
Can you believe it?
I almost can't.
The robust can.
I'm going in.
But...
Closing down chat first.
Okay, let me see if I remember how to play this game.
It's been a while.
It's been, well, five days, I think?
Something like that.
Now, last time...
Look at that.
I made it all the way down here.
And found out that the people living on the ground have houses.
And not only that, but those people are not people at all.
They are, in fact, demons.
And I intend to go down there and teach them a lesson or two about how to demon.
What was I doing?
I went back here because...
Why?
Why did I... Oh yeah, because I'm going to get reset here anyway when I start the game, so...
Yeah.
I have a darkness poster.
We need to put this somewhere.
Somewhere fitting.
Somewhere, like...
In here.
There.
How do you like them apples, sir?
You like darkness?
A hell forge.
Now, call me crazy, but I feel like there was one item that needed this, so...
Let me put it next to my...
Hey, it goes right there.
Perfect.
I can't right-click on that, but I can probably craft things right now.
Obsidian platform?
Obsidian break.
No, no, no.
I don't want to do that.
Actually, I want to talk to Dylan.
Dylan?
Let's see what I got.
A dark soul reaper.
Wait, did I not get any more than this?
I feel like I got a bunch of stuff last time.
I also got a new weapon.
Unless I'm remembering.
Oh yeah, a book.
I got a book.
I got two books, actually.
What just happened there?
I think he just killed a... He killed an owl.
You know what?
Speaking of these books...
So I have this one.
11% damage.
Agile.
Very fast speed.
Also very fast speed.
Using 14 mana casts a demon's scythe.
Let me actually try that again.
It goes through doors.
But it's like...
Weirdly slow in the beginning.
But then it accelerates and explodes in the firework.
Hmm.
So if you spam it...
I guess you can sort of...
Yeah, I guess that's kind of a nice damage.
But...
I mean... Look at this.
Oh wait, I can't hold it.
I have to spam it.
This one is homing, by the way.
It follows enemies, which is crazy.
A trap ghost!
Let's put that there.
And then we also have...
A dark soul reaper.
I feel like these guys need some paintings.
There we go.
How do you like that Dante?
Wait, why can't I...
Oh, he's locked in!
The green dungeon vase.
Put that there instead.
You're freed!
I heard there is a doll that looks very similar to Dylan.
Somewhere in the underworld.
I'd like to put a few rounds in it.
What?
Why would you say that?
And what do you mean?
Hey, I can't do what I do with so many people watching me.
Think Catelyn the nurse... Ah, okay, I've seen this one before.
What the fuck did he just mean?
There's a doll that resembles Dylan and he'd like to put...
Oh wait, I can't...
Ah, shit.
Okay, hold on.
Let's put this somewhere else.
Put this...
Let's put it there.
You get to have that.
That's kind of fitting, I guess, for that little place there.
Obsidian lamp.
And go there.
And then we have an obsidian sofa.
That belongs in there, I think.
And a chair.
Oh, that doesn't make too much sense, actually.
Remove that chair.
Can I open the door here?
I can.
Beautiful.
The candle?
Ah...
Wait, what was this table here?
Wait a minute, I kind of forgot what this was.
The witching table.
Oh, right-click to have more minions.
Oh, okay.
Let me actually quickly test that.
If I take my...
And I still have that, I think.
Where is Abigail?
Maybe I did completely remove it.
Abigail?
Maybe I don't remember where I put it.
Okay, so hold on a second.
There's a doll of the Clothier.
And the Clothier is called Edmond.
And there's apparently also a doll of Dylan somewhere.
I wonder what kind of gameplay mechanic that...
promises.
Man, I could have sworn I still had Abigail somewhere.
Well, alright then.
Let's click this button.
Money goes in.
Items come out.
You can't explain that.
Construction?
Let's put this in here.
And that one.
The candle also goes in here.
Arrow...
Health?
I mean.
Oh, wait, didn't I have an ammo box?
No.
Oh, wait, actually.
Oh, this was all...
Oh, man, I completely forgot my...
system here.
I also have these keys.
All the gems.
I mean, I kind of like my system here.
This is a good system.
The silt.
Oh, silt, hold on.
Silt.
Hey.
Thank you.
And now, quick stack.
The bombs...
Okay, so these things...
Let me put one of them here.
And this is also...
Hold on.
What should I bring?
This one is good to have.
The arrows go in here, I guess.
Increases...
I don't want that.
That sounds bad.
Teleports you home and creates this one, though.
Mmm.
I want to try that today.
The Potion of Return.
Beautiful.
Okay, I think we're about ready to do the deed.
What's happening out there?
Did you know about this?
Driskon.
No wonder Mortal has so many accidents.
You can't imagine how much ale he buys from me.
Oh, yeah?
You know what?
Give me some ale.
I'm going to go down there and get drunk.
Drink.
Before we go...
Let me actually look at my...
Oh, wait, I also have this.
What is in here?
All kinds of stuff, actually.
First, loot all.
And then...
Flop.
Inside of this, I want to put...
potions that I will need in combat.
And utility stuff.
Silts block.
I can use more of that.
Thank you.
Quick stack.
This one is also kind of nice, I guess, to have.
That goes in here as well.
There we go.
The golden keys can go in there.
Potion of Return can stay.
The ale stays, of course.
Now...
I had food here.
Look at this.
Minor, medium.
Let's bring some seafood dinners.
We're going to have buffs down there.
And I think we're ready.
We're ready to rock and roll.
Now, I made a sort of quick path down here.
And I also have an item...
that...
negates fall damage.
So...
isn't that cool?
No longer shall I take fall damage...
in this game.
We're just going to be so weird to get used to.
It's actually so weird being back in this game.
It's been...
feels like longer than five days to me.
Okay, so just straight down.
Don't... don't question it too much.
Just go.
See, here I thought maybe I could make a little...
railway down.
But that wouldn't make too much sense.
I think it's faster to just drop down.
Maybe I can even...
later on make a completely straight path down.
Because that way I can just fall.
The whole way down.
Hey, you're there.
You are confused.
Man, that guy...
gave me a lot of damage just now.
Also, what am I...
I have the meteor stuff on.
Yeah, I think I still want that.
I do like using the sapper.
Do...
Oh, wait a minute!
Fire hurts.
This is maybe bad.
I had potions last time to protect me from that.
And now I don't.
There's fire everywhere down there, right?
That's bad.
It's kind of bad.
But fuck it.
I believe.
We just have to play it smart.
Especially because today is the first time in forever that I'm not gonna die.
Yeah, you heard that right.
Death's none today.
So check this out.
It's homing.
Where do I want to go?
I think I just want to go right.
Fuck off, whatever you are.
Now, I was looting this place.
Obsidian dresser?
Yeah, you see, I'll take all of these things because I can make sick houses with it.
I've been here already.
I've been in there too.
I remember this now.
Yep, I remember.
So I think I want to go...
I can also go left.
But I kind of want to go right.
Let's go right first.
And so there's lava everywhere.
We've got to be careful.
A fire imp.
And a... what does it say?
Hellbat.
Oh, also, let's do auto-pause on.
Very nice to have that on.
Okay.
Got lava there.
Let me actually put some lights.
Wait, obsidian workbench?
Oh, wait, that's probably just a normal workbench.
Just with obsidian, of course.
I thought it would be like something new.
What's that?
Demon torch.
I feel like I should remove these, by the way.
Maybe they will spawn enemies.
There's money.
Thank you.
That's a lot of money.
In fact...
Wait, what?
Oh, it's because I have this thing on.
Put all the money in.
In case I die.
Give me the screen poster.
Man,
this is so much gold down here.
One gold in one jar?
That's kind of crazy.
Living gore.
At Craig.
Obsidian candles.
I feel like the demon torch is definitely...
So demon, we've got to remove it.
It's going to cause trouble.
Can I actually...
I can remove this, so I should be careful removing the sides here, otherwise lava is going to flow in.
I see a demon torch.
No, that's an obsidian...
Yeah, you know what, I'll take it.
I'll take it.
Okay.
It's going pretty well so far.
In this fucking place.
Look at the background, by the way.
This is pretty much hell itself.
Hellbound banner.
Okay.
Now, this one I want to remove.
That one's going to most likely spawn some demons.
We don't want that.
Torches.
The demon torch.
I wonder if that is a material.
It is!
Okay, interesting.
What's that?
Another hell forge.
I will take it, I guess.
Um, I guess I go this way?
Oh!
Uh-oh!
Oh, I'm taking a lot of damage here, from something.
What is damaging me?
What's happening?
Also, hold on a second.
Oh, wait a minute!
Dude!
It just occurred to me.
First off, drink more ale.
Drink that shit.
I can use...
Where's this item I had?
Where's the book I had on me?
Ah, fuck.
Did I leave it at home?
It must have gone in when I auto-stacked.
Shit.
Anyway, what I was about to say, there was a bat flying around here.
I can go through the walls with that weapon.
And I can actually take care of him.
So, that's the advantage of that weapon.
I'm gonna bring that next time.
Okay, lots of lava.
More houses on the right.
Look at the background.
We've got flying thingies.
Yeah!
Oh, oh, I'm scared.
Okay.
Wait, have I been here?
Why is there stuff there?
Magic power potion!
Yo, that's exactly what I need.
When it comes to it.
Not right now, though.
Let me put some light here.
I can't see shit.
Bro, this is the place to form money!
Holy crap!
What the fuck?
What's that?
We've got a demon!
Come here.
See, if I had this weapon...
Oh, I have an idea.
Oh my god!
How is this weapon not amazing?
It's gonna kill things off screen!
Okay, that actually was a little bit scary to me, though, right there.
Oh, I've got no more mana.
Let's be careful here.
Wow!
You got smacked.
What's that?
Obsidian workbench.
Gotcha.
Man, look at all the lava here.
Oh, that's scary.
Kinda wanna make a house down here.
I'm not gonna lie, that would be kind of dope.
Uh, remove these.
Get out of here.
Uh, a star?
Thank you.
Oh, there's actually stuff up here as well.
Wait, why won't it...
Ah, I see, I see.
Uh, what was the trick I had last time?
Oh yeah, right.
Just spam these buttons and I can go up.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Get rid of these...
What are they called?
Hellbats.
I can't not think of Starcraft when I hear that word.
Oh, see ya.
That guy got...
Oh, look, a cave down there!
I wonder if that means anything other than just background.
Wait, Fireblossom, I need that for some kind of recipe, I remember.
Now, how am I gonna do this?
This seems... Oh, actually, of course, I can just...
Why do I keep thinking I can't just do this?
I don't trust in my flying abilities that much.
This reminds me a lot of Minecraft right now.
The thing I'm doing right here?
Very reminiscent of my time in Minecraft.
Oh my god, look at how much there is.
Oh, please get away from me.
I'm about to make a bridge here.
Actually, activate this.
I mean, worst case, if I fall, I can just jump again and fly.
So, I just need to be quick on the trigger there.
That physics just now made zero sense the way just...
to the left.
I think we can't take damage from the lava falls.
See this guy right here?
Will he be able to damage me while I'm in here?
That's what I'm afraid of.
What's damaging me?
Jesus fuck.
That just did a lot.
Thank you.
Oh, wait, this did not get removed.
What's happening?
Oh, a fire imp.
Oh, I see you now.
Oh, he's teleporting as well.
Ah, okay, okay, I see.
I see.
We should probably put up...
Hold on.
Let's do...
This one doesn't need to be there.
I guess this one doesn't either right now.
Do I still have a buff?
I don't.
Let me eat this.
And then put on...
Yeah, I don't even know.
Yeah, I guess.
See?
There.
Just heal up a little bit.
Campfire didn't bring.
That's okay.
I am afraid of the auto or the smart cursor in here.
I don't trust it at all.
I'm going manual.
Thank you very much.
Is that another Hellforge?
It is, okay.
Thank you.
Another magic power potion.
Obsidian lantern.
Oh, we're going even deeper.
What's happening?
Oh, okay, that hurts.
That hurts.
And I'm burning.
I'm burning.
Ooh, six seconds.
Ooh, that's bad.
Yeah, let me not go down.
What is this?
Hellstone.
Wait, is that the thing I need?
Hellstone brick?
Oh, wait a minute.
I got some Hellstone.
Just raw Hellstone, didn't I?
Is that just a Hellstone brick, though?
Am I blind?
Ah, here it is.
Dude, I totally should be mining this.
Holy shit.
Thank you.
Dude, it's even green.
It's like super rare.
I'm taking this down here as well.
The problem is, though, we have...
How am I going to do this?
What is the smart way to do this?
For the future?
I can put this anywhere, right?
So if I fall...
Nice.
That works.
A little bit risky, though, for my taste, but...
Hell yeah, dude.
Yeah.
There's also more down here, by the way.
Oh, man, it's actually everywhere.
Maybe I should be digging in here.
Fuck yeah, I'm doing it.
I can stand on this.
This is all great.
Let's not activate the lava here.
No automatic digging here, that's for sure.
It's very risky.
Oh, man, don't misclick.
Have some light.
Here we go.
Say what?
Where did that come from?
I don't get it.
Why did that just do that?
Huh?
I don't understand.
Um...
I can't even replace this.
But I can do this, I guess.
And then go like, ahh, this is bad.
Hmm.
Okay, you know what?
Let's wait a bit with that.
Let me keep exploring.
Oh, we've got enemies here.
Holy crap.
Oh, he's about to shoot things!
Yeah, look, they go through...
Even for the enemies here.
Oh!
Fuck off.
Please.
Thank you.
Actually, I should be using this while it has mana.
It's the superior weapon while the mana is there.
Can I remove this again?
Hell yeah.
Okay, now...
Assume.
Can I make that?
Oh, of course I can, I can just...
Do that?
Of course!
I'm a such a dummy.
Uh, what is that?
A demon!
Oh, it's a fire imp.
Get away from me.
Gimme that.
And let me also put this back.
I'm playing it so cautiously here.
Click on that like this.
There we go.
Nice and cozy.
This is my home now.
Look at this glorious thing.
Dang, that was all the gold is just picked up randomly there.
There we go.
Man, I'm getting rich, holy fuck.
What's that?
Can I thread the needle here?
No.
There's actually nothing down there I want.
Actually, that's not true.
I want living gore.
Who doesn't want living gore?
This guy shoots through the walls, that's dangerous.
He needs to be taken care of immediately.
We've got a chest!
I'm excited to see what's in there.
I wonder if this will remove the projectiles being shot at me here.
Probably not.
If they go through houses.
No, wait, is that...
Brisk Obsidian Rose.
Reduces damage from touching lava.
I feel like that's pretty good right here.
What is fire blocks anyway?
Maybe this one I can change.
Let me have this on instead.
I feel like that is way more useful here.
So, okay.
I think I know what this is.
This is the shadow key.
So what I'll be doing...
Is...
Quick stack.
I'm gonna try this potion now.
The potion of return.
Just like Diablo, basically.
Why did I just go back?
I just forgot.
Hold on, why did I just...
Oh yeah, right, the key.
The key!
Where did I put that?
Also, I should turn this off while I'm here.
Key, key, key.
Michelinius.
It's not there, it's not there.
Oh, keys.
Heck yeah, dude.
I have four of them.
They go straight in the money trough.
Bop, bop, bop.
One of them I keep on me.
And now we click on this.
Everything goes in.
Ash blog in.
Fire blossom is organic.
And I guess all this stuff goes up here.
All the decoration is the word I was looking for earlier.
Yeah.
The hook is Michelinius.
Demon torch.
Honestly, I...
What can I make with this?
Tell me about the demon torch.
A demon campfire.
Yep.
That is definitely...
Hold on, Hellstone.
Now...
I don't know.
How?
How do I do this?
Hellstone bar.
Requires obsidian.
I have that.
Obsidian.
Horse.
Oh, I have a lot.
Hey!
Look at that.
Oh, only five.
Wow.
I thought I could make way more.
Dang.
They must be really valuable.
Okay, Dylan, tell me about the Hellstone bar, will ya?
Ooh, here we fucking go.
What's that?
Drill...
Drill containment unit.
Summon's a writable drill mount.
Left click to mine blocks.
Right click to mine walls.
Holy shit.
Oh, God.
A lava-proof bug net.
Holy crap.
Oh, this is a lot of defense.
Melee speed too.
Imp staff.
Summon's an imp to fight for you.
18 summon damage.
That's actually kind of... a lot.
And it requires...
17?
Am I... that's a very specific and odd number.
Literally, it's an odd number.
100% big pig-axe power.
Ooh.
I gotta go for this one, though.
I mean, as soon as I can.
That's gonna be the first one I make.
For sure.
Holy shit, that's 30% extra.
Dude.
What's that?
Oh, the helmet.
Molten 33, though.
Lights, wooden arrows ablaze.
Flammerang.
Awesome.
Okay, well, I have plans then.
But first...
Let's put the stuff back.
Hellstone.
The Hellforge can go in construction.
There it is.
So all of this stuff here, such as that.
And...
that and this.
And these...
Go up here, actually.
This is like the...
decorative chest.
I kind of forgot about the past statue.
I need to use that as well.
Ah, but wait.
Potions?
What do I have?
Ah, there.
Anything here I should be bringing?
Water walking.
Calming builder, danger sand sonar, wormhole.
So here's the thing.
I discovered this last time.
This is the trick to seeing all the different potions here.
You give him water.
Because look at this.
I need to find the one that makes me immune to lava.
Let's see, which one would that be?
Inferno?
Ignites nearby enemies?
This one seems pretty dope as well, honestly.
Endurance potion.
This one as well.
Danger sands.
Night owl.
Fuck, I don't know which one it is.
This one.
Obsidian skin potion.
Fire blossom, water leaf, and obsidian.
Ah, I think I have one fire blossom.
Yeah, water leaf.
I don't think I have any of that.
Nevermind.
I do.
And then the last part was obsidian.
Let me make that.
Gimme!
I need it.
That's gonna be for emergencies.
Can go there.
And this one can go here.
And then...
Oh, it doesn't even work.
Put this in here then.
Organics.
In you go.
There.
Potions.
Alright, we're ready!
Let's go.
Let's try the portal now.
Hopefully it doesn't disappear after a certain amount of time.
Oh no, it's actually on the map too.
Return portal entrance.
Hey!
And now...
Oh no.
Okay, thank god.
Here we go.
Actually, hold on.
There we go.
Okay, let's see.
Broken sunfury.
Wow, it's broken and it still does a lot of damage.
Treasure magnet.
Dynamite.
Heartreach.
This one though is nice.
Recall and torch.
Thank you.
This is a special looking chest too.
Shadow chest.
Pretty dope.
Now, did I explore all the way down there?
I think I did.
Oh!
I need this.
Can't leave that behind.
Don't you follow me.
Shoot him!
There we go.
I really should be using this one.
Actually, I should just clean the area a bit before I go.
Clean it up.
There we go.
I see another fire blossom.
That's very important.
We can make that.
Fire blossom seeds!
And another magic power.
I feel like I should just drink that.
There we go.
Go up here.
Gimme all that.
Oh yeah.
Hellbat banner.
I should put that.
There.
Gimme that.
Nice.
Hold on, can I do something crazy here?
What about this move?
Oh, okay.
That's a bit too much.
So many good weapons right now.
I'm swimming in good weapons.
Oh no, not that guy on the right.
That's annoying.
Oh, I forgot to bring my item that will shoot through walls.
That's unfortunate.
Hello.
Hey.
There's nothing down there for me.
Okay, just go up.
Just go up.
Everything's fine here.
Gonna make a little hole.
Don't you shoot shit at me.
Luckily, he only starts to shoot at me when he has line of sight on me.
Imagine if he just kept shooting.
That would be terrible.
So there's lava below me.
Oops, oops, oops, oops, oops.
Let me regen real quick.
Yeah, just use a potion.
Hup!
Oh, that was close.
I kind of want to grab this.
Hellstone.
Thank you.
This is gonna be...
No, no, no, no, no, no, you're not gonna do that.
Oh!
Hello.
Nope, wrong button.
Don't you fucking do that.
Oh, it's so good.
Whew.
Just leave this banner here, honestly.
If they are here, it means it's good for me.
It will increase my damage.
Dude, I love loading these things down here.
Oh, here we go!
A demonic hell card provides seven seconds of immunity to lava.
Holy shit!
It's actually useful!
Uh...
Wait, how do I...
Hell yeah, dude!
I guess I can put it here.
Restoration potion.
Ninety life reduced potion cooldown?
See, that seems pretty good.
Inmissibility, life force, potion of return!
And a Hellwing bow.
Dude, all this loot.
It's amazing.
What's that?
You see that?
Obsidian Watcher banner.
Just put it back, I guess.
Hanging up.
I thought it was like a bat hanging from the ceiling or something.
Okay, what do we got?
Look at this little quaint room down here.
Who's having dinner there?
Huh?
Hand to Earth?
I'm taking this.
I need...
Door to lava!
I don't want to open that door, I don't think.
That's bad.
Oh my god, look at all the loot down there.
Uh, but we've got lava here.
Oh!
We're fine.
Thank you.
Gimme that as well, that looks badass.
Skelehead.
Now, I want to mine for more of this stuff here.
I need to take the ones I can get here.
Ah, there's lava there.
Oh, wait!
I should have brought a bucket of water.
Dude, that's the solution here.
Or maybe even a dirt bomb, actually.
Will that override the lava is the question here.
Uh, first, quick stack.
No, not, oh no.
Depositol, thanks.
Uh, put this back here.
And give me this.
Give me... sure.
And these ones.
Reco... no.
Wait, why do I have four of these?
Oh, they don't get used!
Oh!
That's pretty dope.
I guess.
Fireblossom seeds.
So, this item right here.
Where is it?
This one.
Could actually, depending on how big of a range that is.
Let me change that.
I want to see how good that is.
Whoa!
Wait, what did I just...
Oh no, I picked them up from taking it from the...
Okay, I see, I see.
Obsidian break, delete that.
So, if I go like...
that...
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, that works.
That works wonders.
But the problem is, I can't mine from that distance.
That's the bottleneck here.
Crap.
Welp.
That's unfortunate.
Ah, we got a demon there.
Excuse me, how did you even get in here?
So, it doesn't use... but default here, use the restoration...
Oh wait, it's in my thingy.
That's wrong.
So, the restoration potion...
This one.
If I put it there, I wonder if that will auto-use that.
It will prioritize it.
Give me the obsidian clock.
Probably tells time, amazingly.
Let me remove these.
Please, just get away from me.
Look how amazing that is.
Oh, oh shit, oh shit.
He didn't even die.
Now he's dead.
See ya.
You meanie.
Let's wait a bit, let's just heal up.
Let's play this ultra-safe.
Let's see here.
Man, I guess this lasts for the entirety of the world, right?
That's kind of insane.
Oh, hell butterfly?
I bet I can catch that with the lava net.
Yeah,
just clean up the area before anything happens here.
Okay, let's go.
Just kill them all.
Up, there.
Up.
Come on.
Nice.
Very nice.
Let me gain access to this place.
Titan potion.
Increases knockback.
I love looting.
Oh no, not you.
You're so annoying.
You're just like those mages up in the real world there.
I guess this is the real world, just very down.
What is that?
Oh my god, it's an obsidian workbench again.
Ah, look at the distance at which I pick up now.
Definitely bigger.
So I'm gonna take this.
Wait.
Lava?
Wait, I don't understand.
Does lava come out of the hellstone itself?
That I don't understand.
I'm scared.
Come on, get away, get away, get away, get away.
Come on.
There we go.
Whoops.
One gold in that.
I don't think these demon torches here actually spawn demons because there's no demons here.
I've been here for a while.
Never mind, there's one there.
Come here.
What is he holding?
Wait!
Oh!
Hold on a second!
Is that Dylan?
Look at the hair!
Dylan, I'll rescue you!
Hang tight!
This is what was talked about!
Where'd he go?
Look!
Dylan!
You are a terrible person.
Huh?
Well, I'm gonna bring that back to the guy up there.
What was his name?
Not Mortz Hall, the other guy.
The weapons dealer.
Hey!
Oh my god, I can't fucking...
You know, this weapon right here is meant for people like me who can't aim for shit.
I don't mind.
That's just how it is.
He was fucking carrying that guy around.
I wonder what that even means.
I'm gonna be doing an expedition up here now.
Oh!
Thank you!
Casually picking up 20 Hellfire arrows.
What is that, a magma snail?
Oh, oh, oh!
Hold on.
Who's actually...
It's you!
Menacing obsidian rose.
Another one of these.
Plus 4% damage.
That's actually kind of cool.
That's a... 4% is not bad.
Right?
I feel like I want that instead.
The other one I had was...
1% movement speed.
I like this more.
Heal up.
Um...
Oh, I see fire blossom.
Very important.
Oh, that was close!
Um...
Actually, hold on.
I see something over here I want to mine.
So, okay, so the Hellstone actually spawns lava when you destroy it.
Okay, I have an idea.
Guys, this is it.
I am gonna consume...
the obsidian potion.
Wherever it is.
And I'm just gonna go ham on mining.
While it lasts.
So, um...
Let me equip...
this one.
And also, this one.
Like that.
Uh...
Oh, I could even bomb shit.
Oh, hold on now.
Hold on now.
I have to lead these, I guess.
I don't really...
You know what?
Fuck off.
I don't really want that.
Obsidian brick.
Right.
I think that's it.
We have to activate it first, so let's put it...
there.
There we go.
And now...
Also eat this.
And then...
Also...
Hmm.
I don't think there's anything else I want to be consuming.
We're just gonna go right into it.
But where's that thing I just, uh...
Man, my inventory.
I suck.
I have a severe case of I can't see shit.
There we go.
So now, everything should be fine.
I can go nuts.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Dude, I want to go all the way down.
Let's go all the way down.
Oh, baby.
Down, down, down, down, down, down.
Down we go.
I want to see what's at the very bottom of the world.
We're going all the way down.
Dude, look at all the hellstone we're gonna get.
And this lasts for six minutes.
Uh-oh, we've got a dude.
I don't want dudes.
Not right now.
I'm in a fragile state.
I'm mining.
Dude, this is so quick.
Come on.
There we go.
Further down.
I have no fear.
Actually, before we go further...
Uh, quickly, quick stack.
Why is the money not going in?
Okay, so I'm a little confused here.
I have a piggy bank at home that you can put money in.
But I thought the piggy bank was shared with the money trough.
Like, it was the same item, so to speak.
Except you can't bring the piggy bank with you and, you know...
Actually, I guess you could.
But you probably can't pick it up with items in it.
So, I don't understand why...
Yeah, I don't understand.
Maybe I misunderstood that.
I probably did.
Give me all the hellstone holdies.
Dude, I'm not going home until I have...
Bags full of this stuff.
Oh, let me bomb, actually.
Oh, wait, that's not doing anything to these.
Oh, interesting.
Right, okay.
I guess that's why my piggy access can mine hellstone.
Because it's actually kind of a big thing.
It's a big deal to be able to do this.
Rock bottom.
The only way is up.
Wait, really?
I can't go further?
Oh, I guess I can't.
My screen isn't moving anymore.
Okay, cool.
I have trouble seeing my character right now.
Dude, I got to take a sip of my coffee.
I haven't even touched it.
Oh, I need more, actually.
Hold on.
Okay, I'm ready.
Up we go.
Oh, I can't see myself.
Go.
Oh, no, we've got enemies.
Kind of want to take care of that guy first.
Let's just mine in this direction.
Oh, they're in there.
Oh, there's a guy up there as well.
Just do this, honestly.
Oh, no, it...
There we go.
Give me hellstone.
Lots of it.
Dude, I want to make that drilling rig, whatever it's called.
Ah, that sounded amazing.
I want that so bad.
But I need all kinds of bars for that.
Bars that I suspect will be difficult to acquire.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
Look how much I'm getting.
Three minutes left.
Nice.
Okay.
Actually, I'm going to quickly go take a piss because I'm bursting.
And when I come back, let me know if the audio is okay today, because I actually changed the in-game audio a little bit, and I just remembered to ask you.
So, yeah.
Be right back.
All right.
There we go.
So, is the audio good?
Audio's fine for me.
I just assumed you would clear chat in case...
It is okay?
Perfect.
Okay.
Awesome.
I'm just going to continue on.
Okay, I've got three minutes left, so I only used half my time so far.
I need more.
We are not done.
Uh-oh.
That's kind of scary.
That's actually kind of scary.
We're okay.
Heal up.
Look at this.
It became a fossil inside the ash.
That's actually kind of fun.
That actually looked like it belonged there in a weird way.
Continue on.
Just go here.
Oh, yeah.
This is such fast mining as well.
I can't even see my character.
He's just completely obscured by lava.
One minute.
Oh, here we go.
I was ready that time.
Let me take this and then I'm going to fuck off.
Okay.
Time to fuck off.
Let's go.
I'm scared.
Thirty seconds.
Oh, we're fine.
Okay.
Nice.
We did it.
We diddly done it.
Let me put on this one now.
Actually, I don't know if that's better than this.
Reduces.
I mean, it depends how much damage is being reduced here.
Right?
Like, how much are we talking?
I kind of want to test it.
I will test it.
Dark Soul Reaper.
Just give me that.
We're back to a non-smart cursor now.
I do not trust.
Bro, this weapon is freaking fantastic.
Oh, God.
Okay, there's actually a smart way to test if there's enemies.
If the projectile bends, you know they're there.
You know?
It's a cool way to check for enemies off-screen.
Decreased Light Vision.
What?
Oh, oh!
My gut spawned right behind me.
I wonder if I took less damage from that attack just now, because of my menacing obsidian rose.
This is just a Luc Pinata, this place.
I am taking all the paintings, though.
Hey.
Thank you.
I need that.
Why can't I break this?
Oh, it's... okay, I see.
I understand.
And there's nothing else down here that I really want.
How much do I have of this now, by the way?
293!
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
That's really cool.
Hey.
There we go.
Ah!
I'm not taking damage from this, curiously.
What is that up there?
Oh, is that a gem?
Let me actually get that.
No, no, no, no, no.
I need it.
I want it.
Ah, not you.
You're annoying.
Okay, so it used the Quick Potion now.
40 seconds, though?
That's still a long time, isn't it?
Maybe it was a minute before, I don't know.
In which case, it's actually kind of significant, I gotta say.
In that case, it's kind of fast.
Still a long time, though.
Okay.
This is a big...
Is that a piano?
What's up with all these health forges here?
What are they forging down here?
Probably evil items.
Obsidian piano.
Can I... I wonder if I can play it.
No, it doesn't look like it.
That's sad.
I wanna play the piano.
Let's move on.
This is exciting.
Ah, let's not go that way.
Let's just go through the... here.
Let's play it smart.
Speaking of smart, look at all this.
You may think, why do you need so much?
And the answer is, I don't know.
I just do.
And through the door.
What's up, guys?
How's it hanging?
So, the good thing about those flying demons there, they don't really use their attack unless you are...
Unless you haven't attacked them for a while, it seems.
So you can sort of suppress them a little bit, by keeping up the attacks.
Thank you.
Man, I'm getting so rich in here.
Holy shit.
When that merchant comes by, you know I'm gonna be buying his whole stock.
You already know.
No.
I just took damage from something.
There's nothing down there of value, it seems.
I guess I'll go up.
Whoa, these are fire blossoms.
They don't even look like it.
What the heck?
Oh, that one wasn't.
Oh, this is gonna be a little questionable, isn't it?
Fire blossoms.
Now, this is a house.
Look at this.
Oh, wait a minute.
We need one of these.
Quick stack and then also take it back.
Let's see.
A masterful flame lash.
What is that?
Summon's a controllable ball of fire.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Ornate shadow key.
Summon's a pet shadow mimic.
Really?
Alright, let's do it.
Oh, nice.
Meteorite.
Oh, obsidian skin potions.
And rave items.
I don't want that.
I do want this chest, though.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You.
There we go.
Another chest.
Oh, I love these chests.
Unpleasant dark lands.
Dude, I'm gonna be testing so many weapons later.
Amazing.
Delete this.
Meteorite, tungsten bullets.
Oh, nice.
Bro, this is incredible.
The loose down here is never...
You saw that?
A mimic.
I don't believe it.
That's unreal.
Is it this one?
Come on, wake up.
Wake up.
Wait.
Wait, is that...
Oh, it's mine!
I'm such an idiot.
Oh my god.
Jesus Christ.
Wow.
The way it's following me and opening its mouth, it makes me think I'm being attacked.
All the time.
Goddamn.
Demon's Eye.
Really?
Now this I will take damage from, but I have this on, so let's see how much...
Oh, maybe not actually.
Lulu in the traveling merchant.
You know what?
We're going back.
I need to see what's in stock and we have special potions that will take us back.
Somewhere.
There we go.
Actually, let me turn this off now anyway, because I'm going back.
Here we are.
Lulu then.
Where?
Judo.
Ella?
Who the fuck are you?
Wait, who's that?
Triskan offered me a root beer.
I told him to give it to me in a square cup.
What the fuck?
Yo, what the heck is that?
What is all this?
Whoa.
Whoa, what?
Hold on now.
Wait, is this the redstone stuff of this game?
Mechanical ruler.
Pixel box.
Oh, okay.
Interesting.
A wire cutter.
Ah, all right.
Five second timers and shit like that, huh?
Booster track.
Hammer to change direction.
Wait, plus two range?
Okay.
Now this though, hold on.
Mechanics rot.
Thirty five percent.
I don't know if that's better than what I have.
Wait, did I even put it in here?
Oh, yeah, I did.
Twenty two.
Oh, my God, it's way better.
I mean...
Spaghet!
Burp, please get away so I can click on...
There.
Oh, here's the thing though.
I have...
Ooh, I have a lot of savings.
Okay.
Before I buy this, let me check Llewelyn, wherever she or he is.
Sparkle?
Oh,
it's up there.
Oh, you're on the roof!
I'm coming to you.
Sir, what do you got?
I sell only what I can get.
Edmund keeps hounding me for exotic clothing.
Oh, yeah.
The G.
Uh...
Equipable.
Five percent increase damage in critical strike chance.
Ten percent increase in melee and movement speed.
Oh.
I mean...
Someone's a baby harpy?
One platinum?!
Bro.
No fucking way.
The bereaved.
Yes.
I shall take the bereaved.
The G is not a material and it doesn't seem insanely useful to me because I'm not really...
Well, I'm buying it anyway.
What's this?
Oh, it's silt.
Put something else in there for now.
Something like...
You know what?
This one.
What is that?
Yeah, put that in there.
Nobody needs that.
Okay.
While I'm up here...
Let me click this.
Blop.
Such a good feature.
And then...
I'm going to try these new weapons.
Masterful flame lash.
Oh, controllable?
Oh, so it's just like the other one.
Yeah, throw it that way.
Throw it that way.
That's actually really cool.
So it's sort of like the other one I have.
The unpleasant dark lands.
Like a spear.
Kind of fast.
41.
I guess I could test the DPS here.
Let me actually do that.
So this is better at a certain range.
But you need to be at a very specific range here.
For that to work.
And then this one...
I mean, that's not...
Oh, but it uses mana.
Right.
Yeah.
But hold on, if I...
Oh, that also consumes mana while I'm holding it.
If I... If it hits something...
That costs mana.
And it does put them on fire, actually.
But it's not a lot of damage.
It's like one damage.
But you can totally...
Have fun with that, you know?
Just...
Okay, I'm out of mana.
Cool.
Put this back here.
Awesome.
Are these mats at all?
No.
The bereaved.
We gotta have this picture somewhere.
Running out of space, I realize.
But it's very important.
Get rid of that.
There we go.
The bereaved goes in there.
And then let's put the star statue...
I actually haven't noticed any more stars than usual.
Maybe it doesn't work.
Then again, I haven't... Oh yeah, this one.
Guide voodoo doll.
Uh, Dylan?
Look what I found.
Oh wait, it's not even...
A material.
I can't ask you about it.
Okay.
I hear a raise of lizard men live in the jungle.
Maybe you can get the attention of one by felling a giant beast of the jungle.
Oh, is that how I'm gonna...
No, wait a minute.
I was thinking about the one temple place that I couldn't gain access to.
That wasn't a desert, was it not?
It was like a desert temple.
Underground.
The one I excavated all around.
Stylist.
Not all of the undead monsters are hostile.
I hear one sells merchandise.
Waiting slime.
I'm just gonna click through to see if there's anything new.
Rare fossils and many hazards?
Yep.
Marble biome.
Be careful.
They say that those locations are inhabited by some very dangerous creatures.
And granite biomes.
The very stone itself is a threat.
Frequently coming to life and attacking intruders.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Yeah, I haven't seen a fairy in a while.
The underworld is made of a material called hellstone.
It's perfect for making weapons and armor.
When you're ready to challenge the keeper of the underworld, you will have to make a living sacrifice.
Everything you need for it can be found in the underworld.
Keeper of the underworld.
Normally, I try to teach you all about the old one's army.
But you should probably ask Driskin about that.
Oh yeah, speaking of that, I think I have everything I...
I am very powerful now.
I can definitely do that, I believe.
He says, and then obviously can't do it.
We'll see how it goes.
You know what?
I'll keep these items for now.
Maybe they will become useful in that battle.
Let's see here.
This one, not that useful right now.
I will put this back.
But I guess... four extra defense?
So five is an increased damage and critical strike chance.
Does that apply to range it too?
Four percent crit?
If I put this on...
Wait, why can't I...
Oh, it's an...
Oh, it's... I mean, obviously it looks like a piece of armor.
But I actually thought it was...
something for down here.
Because these are boots, right?
But they don't go in the boot slot.
So it's confusing.
Okay.
Well, in that case, it's not really that useful.
At least to me.
Put the paintings in here.
The piano.
All that good stuff.
These roses here.
Four percent damage.
Actually, not bad, I guess.
But you go in there.
Oh, wait.
It is a... Actually, it is a material.
I'm going to check that too.
This is not a material.
This is a material.
I need to check that.
Okay.
Dulan!
I have a job.
This is just shake hands.
No, they're doing the thing.
Stop doing the thing.
Lava waiters.
Provides the ability to walk on water, honey and lava.
Grants immunity to fire blocks and seven seconds of immunity to lava.
Reduces damage from touching lava.
But I can't fly them.
Lava charm?
I don't have that.
I don't even have this.
But there's multiple paths here.
I think I have this.
I'm not sure, actually.
Didn't I have something where I could walk on water?
Magma skull?
Hmm.
Obsidian skull rose.
Wait.
Obsidian skull.
I have that.
Otherwise, I can craft that, no?
Obsidian skull.
It's not here.
Organics.
Hmm.
Give me obsidian.
Oh, and I'm also going to bring my water bucket next time because I want to make obsidian.
I need more of it.
Where did I put it?
Probably Michelin is, right?
Yeah, water bucket.
Bring in that.
Good thing I remembered.
What else do I have in here?
Lens.
I guess I can bring one of these.
Do that.
Now, this right here is still intriguing to me.
It's connected to...
that desert temple place.
Silt block.
I know what I want to do with that.
There we go.
Ella, I will actually be purchasing from you before I forget.
Let me have this.
Thank you.
Also, is this a material?
It's not.
Is it gems?
Tungsten bullets?
Eh.
Honestly, nah, deleted.
I don't want that shit.
This one can go away as well.
We can sell that.
We have two Muramasas.
Nah, just keep it, I guess.
Aqua Scepter.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, I just had an idea.
Sprays out a shower of water?
Obsidian?
I'm testing both of these.
Maybe it doesn't work, because it's a weapon, but we'll see.
Okay, Luling is gone.
That's fine.
Let me do this now.
Make one of these.
Oh, wait, no.
It costs 20.
That's too much.
Because I want to make the other things.
Wait.
Here?
No, here?
Give me...
Fuck, where is it?
Where's my Hellstone?
Wait a minute, I had...
Oh, it's in my thing, probably.
Ah, here we go.
Loot all.
Quick stash?
Oh, yeah, this one.
I kind of want to try and repair that.
And the shadow chests.
Let's put them here instead.
They actually light up the area a little bit.
That's nice.
I do like that.
Delete these.
So, I guess I don't need all four of these shadow keys.
But I will keep them just in case I need them at some point.
I don't know.
Maybe there's something I can do with them at some point.
Let's put this one in here.
And I guess this one can be...
sold.
Okay.
Gulan?
I need help with the treasure magnets.
Oh, damn.
Oh, wait a minute.
I have... I have almost all of this.
I need an architect gizmo pack.
Increases block and wall placement speed.
Oh, this one looks like it's made from multiple others as well.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
That seems a little... not good.
Let me try the other one I had.
Didn't I have another item?
Oh, give me these.
Thank you.
Man, didn't I just...
Hold on a second.
Maybe it's still in here.
Oh, yeah, I still have things here.
Noodle.
Stack.
Let me just put this stuff in here.
Oh, I also have this hellwing bow.
Delete chest.
Gimme.
And put it in.
Obsidian vase.
Or vase.
Actually, I don't know which way it is.
Skelehead.
Okay.
Let's sell some stuff.
Hano!
Would you take the flash catcher, please?
And also this one.
I don't need that shit anymore.
Yeah, take it.
It's not a material.
Take this as well.
What else should I sell?
Alright.
So far, so good.
Let me try and repair that now.
That's you.
Reforge.
Broken Sunfury.
Ooh.
Oh, I sell this Sunfury 64.
Oh, it's only a little bit better than this.
But it has...
It has very high critical strike chance, though.
So that's nice.
I think it's better than what I have.
This has 10% knockback.
Yeah.
I'm going with that now.
We're going from blue to red, boys.
And this is not a material, is it?
No.
But I will put it in my weapons locker.
Just in case I need it.
Or something at some point.
Who knows?
You never... Oh, and this time I...
Oh, wait a minute.
Not there.
Let me take one of these with me now.
Before I forget again.
There.
Okay, good.
Good, good, good.
Fire blossom!
We can make stuff with that, but not right now.
Put it in here.
I also have the seats.
The treasure magnet.
Yeah, let's put that in here for now.
Golden key.
See, here's the thing.
These are not being...
Are they being consumed when you use them?
I actually don't know.
The shadow keys are not.
And I seem to remember having six golden keys forever.
Maybe it's my memory messing with me.
The hellwing bow.
Let's try that.
What am I shooting?
I'm shooting jester's arrow.
22 range... I mean...
Hold on, let me actually test the DPS of that.
Wait, why is it so...
Why is it shooting up here?
Huh?
Hold on, I'm so confused.
Wait a minute.
It's shooting randomly.
What the fuck is this?
I don't understand.
Whatever.
That's a shitty bow, it seems.
And that's like shitty accuracy.
What the heck is that all about?
You go in there for now, I'll play with you later.
Ancient chisel.
Man, I have so much stuff in my inventory, but I kind of want to keep it all.
You know what I mean?
I want all of it.
Put all this... Ah, this one goes in here.
These go in here.
Do I have my shadow key?
Or did I put that in here?
I did.
Sneaky sneaky.
This one is nice to have.
And this one is...
Put that in there.
This one, though.
Could be...
Could be nice.
Let's play a bit with that.
Let's take it with us.
The guide voodoo doll?
Bro...
What is even going on with these?
I guess I'll... Can I actually place them in the world?
Can I put a little doll of Dylan next to him or something?
Hey, Dylan, look, I got a doll of you.
Here.
Look at that.
Nah, okay, fair.
It goes in there.
Oh, yeah, this is what I wanted to do.
I wanted to find my hellstone.
Because it somehow disappeared on me.
And I don't believe it.
Let's see here.
There it is.
Okay, it is there.
I'm just blind.
Make hellstone bars.
Ooh, 25 of those.
That means we can now craft things.
Yeah.
What can we make?
Ooh, man.
Oh, man, oh, man.
I mean, I gotta go for the molten pig axe.
But wait.
Is this able to mine hellstone, though?
It doesn't say so.
Hmm.
Fast speed.
Very weak.
Knock back.
Fuck it.
I mean, I have to do it.
Plus 4% speed.
Nimble.
Okay.
Flop.
I'm gonna bring both, just for now, in case I actually cannot.
The fact that it doesn't say able to mine hellstone, I don't think I'm able to.
I mean, it's made of hellstone, so maybe it's implied that it is able to.
I don't know.
The sticky bomb.
You know what?
Let's put that here.
It's not really useful right now.
Water bucket.
Yep.
Seafood dinner.
Always good to have.
It's time to go back.
Blop.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Oh, wait a minute.
I should try this maybe now.
Yeah.
What did I need for that?
I think I needed a thing that I bought from this guy.
No?
A shop?
Yeah, give me one of these.
Let's try it one more time.
Let's try.
See how it goes.
I'm gonna put down every single thing I can here to help me out.
So...
Nope.
Wait a minute.
Where's the platform?
Like that.
And then I'm gonna hang this there.
There we go.
Campfire.
There.
Bast statue.
And...
I also had a couple potions.
Let me actually use that.
Dude, if this one goes through enemies, the Masterful Flame Lash, then it could be very good.
Actually.
What did I want to do just now?
Potions.
I need Iron Skin if I have it.
Wait, what is Battle Potion?
No, don't...
That's not what we want.
Fuck, I don't have it.
I can't be arsed to look into how that's crafted right now.
I just can't.
Let's try.
Wait, how do I do this again?
Here we go.
Zoom out.
Let me try this now.
Let me see if it goes through enemies.
Oh, it totally does.
But it sort of curves a little bit.
Well, that's actually a sick weapon.
And then we switch to this one when we're out of the other one.
Maybe even this is good.
Interact with the crystal to rush next wave.
Yeah, sure, why not.
There we go.
Just kill them all.
Now that we have infinite mana.
Oh man, we have good DPS here.
I'm liking this.
Wave complete.
Rush to next.
Okay.
I'm just going to shoot left and right here.
It's going pretty well.
They can't even get into range to hit me.
That's big.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, we're amping things up now.
We've got flying shit.
Should probably take care of that, huh?
Look at them approaching.
Oh, they're shooting me.
Oh, they're approaching.
This is dangerous.
The javelin people.
Did I do it?
Next.
I'm getting lots of defender medals.
I'm focusing so hard.
Oh, they're charging me here.
Uh oh.
Oh no, I'm faltering.
They're hitting the crystal.
Oh no!
Holy fuck!
Yeah, this is bad.
Shit, man.
Damn.
God damn.
I should have just kept using my fucking sapper.
I don't know why I did that.
I was being a little too cautious.
Let me try that one more time.
I think I got it, man.
I got it.
Drisken, I need one more.
Give me this.
Let's try that one more time.
Yo, I just figured out a way to maybe cheat.
Hold on, I have an idea.
Hold on.
I can shoot here.
Pause.
Change my cursor to the left.
Continue and shoot.
Because my problem is, I'm inaccurate.
I'm actually gonna try that.
The game does pause.
If it gets hectic, I'm gonna use that.
Like I can go here and then shoot.
I can aim up my... I can aim my shots.
You know, I can take my time.
I can go like this.
Oh yeah, dude.
Next.
I mean, right now I don't need it because it's kind of easy.
Maybe I need to switch to this one at the very end.
Nah, it's not actually that good.
This one is definitely the one to go...
to go with here.
This one is king.
Next.
Man, the sapper is insane!
I'm so glad I bought this weapon.
And I've had it for so long now, too.
Like, this is an absolutely amazing weapon.
Honestly...
Like, what the fuck?
What's up with this weapon?
Why is it so good?
Next.
We have flying people now.
There we go.
Pause, aim...
Shoot.
Okay, I actually still missed.
That's incredible.
You didn't see that, guys.
The minimap is actually blocking my vision.
Oh no, I hate these flying things because they distract my shots.
Oh, this is actually... The flying things are causing trouble.
Fucking die!
Okay, I kind of need to heal here.
Holy shit, hold on.
Oh, I should try this as well, actually.
Maybe that will be good if I go like this.
Oh yeah, actually, that could be pretty neat.
It goes through them.
Creative... You have lost the power of creation?
What?
Oh, is that just the debuff telling me I can't build?
That's probably what that is.
Pause, aim... Shoot.
Come on, kill him.
Let me try this now.
Oh, whoa.
What was happening?
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
The flying ones are fucking me.
I need to use this here.
Oh, I died!
Oh shit!
Holy crap!
Like, the flying ones, I need to find a way to deal with them.
The sapper is not it against those.
I can't deal with it.
I cannot deal with it.
You know what, I'm going to leave this here as a reminder that I cannot deal with it.
Yep, that's the reminder there.
Didn't I also put a campfire here?
I'll put it over here, maybe.
Alright, well...
I tried.
I'm going to quickly go back and deposit my shit, and then we go back down on the ground.
I'm not strong enough with this shit yet.
Do that, and then click this lovely button.
Cool!
Let's jump through portal.
And we're back!
Although it was so soon then, it's weird.
Okay.
I'm just going to continue going right here.
Let me just zoom out a little bit.
Kill him, kill him!
This weapon is amazing in those situations where it's really tense.
And you're not sure whether or not you can hit things, and you're in time pressure.
I keep thinking this is an enemy approaching me.
It is not, though... Do I take damage from this?
No.
Give me that.
Man, okay.
I thought these fire blossoms were very rare.
They're actually not rare at all.
They're everywhere.
See ya.
Okay, now, how do I do this in the best way?
Probably just like that, right?
Look at that.
Smooth as heck!
Close one?
I keep thinking that's a chest down there.
I mean, it is, but, you know...
Don't shoot there, shoot that shit at me.
Oh, look at this!
This looks different.
Am I below the...
Ah, look, I am.
I'm below the jungle.
See ya, dude.
Nice.
Look at this place, it looks different.
What's that?
Oh, it's nothing.
I kind of want to go up.
There was something about a great beast in the jungle, right?
And I would gain their respect if I defeated it or something.
Someone's admiration.
Maybe I should just try that.
I just want to go a little further down here.
Just to see, you know.
See ya.
Close one.
Ah, I'm jumping into them.
I keep wanting to click on this chest.
God, this weapon is fantastic for someone like me.
Nice.
Look at the pro movement here.
I keep going.
What's up, dude?
You know what, let's go back up here, actually.
I want to find that great monster.
Spoke enough.
Oh my god.
Where?
Who are you?
Spike, oh, jungle slime.
All right, then.
What is hitting me in here?
Why are there so many of these fire bats?
God, I love this...
Okay, this is actually turning into my...
one of my favorite weapons.
It's that good.
Is this... hold on, is this actually faster?
Am I losing my mind?
Eh!
Wait a minute.
Why does this feel slower?
Hold on.
This is slower!
What the...
Am I fucking losing my mind?
This says 100% pickaxe power.
This says 70%, but...
it feels slower to me.
Am I crazy?
Like, look, it's way quicker.
I'm not crazy, this is real.
What the fuck?
Let me actually put this on, too.
There.
Delete the stone.
Keep the vine, I guess.
Okay, here's my trick now.
I'm gonna go up like this.
I'm gonna spam.
Look at this.
It's so... uh...
What the fuck is that?
What just happened there?
That was so weird.
I have no clue.
Oh!
You there.
Please get away from me, will ya?
Uh, so what do I see around me?
I guess I just wanna sort of dig my way this way.
Back up to the left here.
Sort of connect the whole region.
And for that, I have special items.
What am I taking damage from?
Am I...
Oh, I'm... Oh!
Oh, I'm walking into the thingies.
Okay, I see, I see.
It's a plant.
I get it now.
I also want more of this.
I needed that for something.
Moonglow is nice.
Let me get up there.
Okay, test here.
Where's that weapon now?
Let's equip that on... here.
If I go like this, and I stand here.
Or like there.
Now I wanna try and kill it.
Oh, it doesn't actually go through.
Huh!
Okay.
That's fair, I guess.
Otherwise, that would be a little broken, actually, now that I think about it.
And I'm gonna save my scarab bombs until I recount or something that's actually difficult to mine anyway.
And life crystal, thank you.
What is that?
So let me try this pickaxe again.
Okay, so...
It's...
It's actually faster when it comes to...
certain blocks.
Not all blocks, though.
So I'm gonna have both of them equipped.
And I'm gonna hot-swap between them.
Away you go.
I feel so powerful.
Sky blue flower.
And oh, look at all this down here!
There's so many!
Actually...
Have fun, guys.
50th jungle bat.
What
is this?
Oh, wait, I'm taking damage.
Ah, slime was hiding me.
It was confused.
This place is nuts.
What is even happening here?
Why are there so many of these man-eaters?
Oopsie.
Will you stop?
Something's annoying me.
Hello?
Is it the flowers?
Fuck you, fuck you.
Oh, my God.
What's up with all these life crystals here?
Get rid of all this now.
Oh, my inventory is full.
Jungle bat banner?
Let me actually just hang that.
Because why not?
There.
All.
That's fine with me.
Yeah, I'm gonna keep that equipped.
The ancient chisel.
Where am I going?
Man, I still have a way to go here.
Jungle torch.
Where is this giant beast that people speak of, huh?
What is this here?
Iridescent brick?
Seaweed.
Yeah, dude, a pet turtle?
I would much rather have that.
I don't want this chest following me, it's confusing me.
Another one of these.
Jester's arrow and gold.
Let me take the ivy chest.
There we go.
That is...
I forget the name of that.
But I don't need it.
I'm hearing sizzling.
I'm hearing seething.
Oops.
Up here, I think.
Go.
I want to use these bombs, please.
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What is that sound?
It's not the lava, because that doesn't make that sound.
Is it?
I mean, it could be.
Hey, you.
This thing is actually really good.
The fire weapon there.
What am I taking damage from?
Oh, I'm being shot by these guys.
So much projectile stuff down here.
Ooh, look at that over there.
That looks interesting.
Let's go there.
Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
There we go.
Yeah.
Let's zoom in a bit.
Oh, no.
No.
I need to.
You know what?
I need to bring the potion that shows danger.
100% that's going to reveal that.
Fuck.
I honestly forgot that was a thing.
Click this button.
Everything in?
Dart trap.
Delete it.
Nobody wants it.
Iridescent brick.
Dylan, is that interesting or not?
Tell me.
It's very uninteresting.
Gotcha.
That goes in the trash.
Now, we do have an interesting chest.
No.
There we go.
And this chest is not interesting, so it gets deleted.
The rich mahogany?
Fuck off.
Don't want it.
Miscellaneous.
My favorite.
Let's put in that key.
The ornate shadow key.
Actually, no.
Put it down here instead.
It's an accessory.
In a way.
But then not really.
I mean, it's a curse.
Delete alert.
That could actually not be too bad with what I'm using right now.
You know?
I'm using this a lot.
The masterful magic missile.
That could be pretty dope.
Let me bring that.
Instead of that, let's put that there.
Oh, I need to bring mana potions then, of course.
Potions.
Mana.
So I have only these.
I don't know if I can make better ones.
But that'll have to do for now.
Drink that.
Yeah, I think we're good.
How do we get back?
Oh, shit.
How are we getting back?
I guess we go down from here and just connect it from upstairs.
And then on the way there, I think I want to try and fish a little bit.
I'm going to bring my upgraded and improved fishing rod that I bought.
I want to play with that.
This one.
Very cool.
And this one right here.
Nah.
Keep it here for now.
I'm not an amazing fan of that.
It's cool.
But is it really that cool?
That's the question.
Then I want to bring bait.
What bait do I want to bring?
Master bait?
Maybe.
Just bring a bit of whatever.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
We're off again.
See ya, people.
Look how fast I traversed the area now.
Let's fish here a bit.
Oh, look how cool that looks.
It's all mechanical and shit.
And I'm using purple bait.
Water strider.
That's probably bait.
Oops.
Flounder.
We can do better than that.
35% fishing power.
I guess I'm only using 15% bait power.
I should be masturbating here.
That's how you get the most out of it.
Come on.
Dude, this is taking forever.
Hey, it was worth it, though.
Nothing in it?
Oh, is it because of this?
Oh.
Awarding acolyte.
Oops.
Oh, I had to right click.
What is that?
Increase movement speed plus four defense?
Huh.
You know what?
Let's equip that for a while, since we gotta be traveling.
Hey.
Look at my cute turtle, though.
Did I bring my net?
I didn't.
So you get to die.
Oh, something else died.
That's fine.
By the way, notice how there's no enemies.
Isn't this great?
We get to fish in peace.
I wonder what happened to the old man.
At the entrance to the underground place we went to.
The guy I fought, Skeletron, he was obviously his master, right?
He said, my master will not fight you, whatever.
So I wonder where the old man went.
Whether or not I get to see him again.
An extractinator.
Wow.
I fished that up from this here lake.
Incredible.
I must have some muscles on me.
I should have brought the damn potion that gave me a chance of finding boxes.
What bait am I using right now?
Wait.
Oh, I'm using this one.
You can actually see it on the cursor here.
Thank you.
Oyster!
Shocked oyster.
I'll eat that.
Mmm, delicious.
Raw and wriggling.
I kind of want to just fish a lot in every biome.
See what I can get.
And also fish down in the caves, if I find a nice pool of water.
It almost looks like I have wings.
I'm flying.
I love this turtle.
This is my favorite so far.
A tin can.
Not quite a robust can.
Just a tin.
So many flounders, what the hell?
More crates, more crates.
Hey!
A hundred potion and a lazy falcon blade.
Ah, shit, that was a bit too early there.
Cool.
Ah, man, this is so relaxing.
I can play with one hand.
I can just sit here and sip my coffee while I find iron boxes.
Oh!
It broke.
We're using a butterfly now.
And now we're using nothing.
So rip.
And I can't catch these because I didn't bring my net.
Frick.
Damn it.
Ah, you know what?
Ah, man.
Let me quickly go back.
I gotta bring my bait.
I gotta bring that bait.
Gotta bring the bait.
Should've brought more, huh?
I wanna go fish somewhere else now.
Fishing!
No, fishing.
Give me the master bait.
And also, give me enchanted nightcrawlers.
Actually, give me these instead.
Yeah, yeah.
Give me all of them.
I feel that I run faster right now, just a little bit.
Maybe it's a placebo.
Whoops.
I am flying through this world.
Look at that.
No problem.
While I'm running, casually killing people.
The progression is really nice in this game.
It feels good.
Like, look at that shit.
Compare this to the beginning, where I was shooting my sword.
That's just the funniest animation.
Where am I going?
All the way over there.
Dope, dope.
Here.
Let's see it.
I'm using Journeyman bait.
Seaweed.
Now I'm broke.
What the fuck?
This Journeyman bait sucks.
Can I actually wear this?
I can't...
Why not?
I want to wear the old shoe.
Maybe it could be a vanity item.
Another one!
Someone accidentally dropped both of their shoes in here.
That's incredible.
Real man, fish from the sky.
Funny how the... wait, is the...
The turtle is turning into a helicopter when it flies, look.
What kind of shit is that?
What is going on with this Journeyman bait?
What the...
Hello?
Is there a basic fishing mechanic I'm not getting here?
Okay, here we go.
Okay, now we're rocking.
Now we just need some boxes.
I wonder if I can manually switch bait here.
What if it comes...
oh!
Oh, so it's whatever is first.
Cool.
Glad I figured that out.
Okay, show me the box now.
I want to see iron, I want to see wood, and all kinds of other things.
Okay, there's no boxes here.
This place is bomb fish, is not good for boxes.
How come nobody is littering here, huh?
I just want a place where people litter.
Seaweed.
Also useless.
Frogleg.
Increases jump speed and allows auto jump.
Cool.
Definitely going to be checking that out with the old Dylan.
Please go away.
Looks like night is about to hit, so maybe it's time for us to go down into the earth soon.
Oh, it's raining slimes!
Hold on, we have nine of these now.
When it breaks, we lose one, right?
Let me just double check.
Because I feel like that's not what happens half the time.
More.
Oh, what's that?
A quest item.
Caught in sky lakes and surface.
What?
Is that for the little fishing breath?
Oh, I thought that was a box.
God damn it.
Okay, night is about to hit.
It's time for me to skip.
On out of here.
Oh my god, we walked one tile and the biome switched.
Let me try this now then.
Hold on, we can't go down yet.
I just need to quickly try this too.
Ah, it broke, so now we have still nine.
Okay, so...
Wait.
What?
Let's pay attention.
What actually determines?
Nice.
Oh, a copper bar.
Boo!
More.
Dude, I have a lot of fishing power right now.
I have 75 fishing power.
Actually, 85.
85% fishing power.
I wonder what happens if you get 100 fishing power.
Is it just instant?
You get a bite immediately.
There's no delay.
That's what I wonder.
Maybe there's a potion for that.
In the last bit of fishing power, maybe an item, an equipable item.
I want a fisherman's hat, if that exists.
I want something that boosts my fishing.
Think World of Warcraft.
Wait.
Oh, it was in the...
It was in the jungle we found that temple.
I thought it was in the desert.
Wait, is there even such a thing as a desert?
Am I completely...
gone here from reality?
The fuck?
How did I remember a desert?
Doesn't look like there's a desert actually.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
I was like, oh yeah, it's in the desert.
I was there.
There's no fucking desert.
Where am I going?
Hold on.
Okay, we're gonna try something now.
No matter what.
I don't care.
No.
Get away.
We are going straight down now.
Yeah, straight down.
I don't even care.
Nothing shall get in the way.
Let me quit my thing.
There.
I'm going through this entire jungle.
Straight down.
Because I kind of want to fall from the top of the world to the bottom.
Basically, that's my mission, okay?
Don't ask why.
It's just one of those things that I feel in my heart.
It needs to be done at least once.
It would also probably be pretty cool.
Oh, it's getting dark down here.
Do we have disco lights?
No.
Oh, we do, we do.
Oh, they come with me when I dig!
That's big!
Yo, that's amazing!
The glow sticks!
The fact that they come with me is actually wild.
Oh my god.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Shit.
I wanted to bring my Danger Sense potion.
That was one of the things...
I tried to drink a lake.
I completely forgot that I...
Yep, okay.
Yep.
That's...
Okay.
That did not happen.
We are forgetting about this, but you know what?
This is a perfect opportunity to bring the Danger Sense potion.
In fact, it was on purpose.
It was on purpose.
Construction, go in here.
You probably don't believe me, but it's so not true.
Uh, so do you want this quest item, Izzy?
Awesome catch!
It's all going according to plan.
The fuck are you up to?
I haven't even used the last fish you gave me.
I don't need another.
Uh, what do you mean used?
The fuck?
You have entertained me enough for today.
Go!
You are done!
The Grand Izzy dismisses you!
Izzy?
You are shitty.
That's the best I could come up with there.
That's it.
Okay, well...
What did I even get for that?
Did I get money?
Did I get... Hold on.
Chat?
There's no log of what I got, right?
I'm not sure what's happening here.
Oh, you know what I want to bring?
There's something that boosts my movements.
This one.
I want this on me.
And then potions, before I forget.
Danger sense potion!
Mining potion?
Wait.
Restores from 70 inconsistent potion sickness, brief periods of inexplicable...
You know, that actually sounds pretty dope.
I'm not gonna lie, that actually sounds pretty cool.
That one also is nice to have, I guess.
Alright then, Dylan!
Tell me, what do I do with frog legs?
Oh!
Hold on, one second.
Fuck off!
Alright, Dylan.
Tell me again about the frog legs.
Amphibian boots, they're where I can run super fast.
Increases jump, increases...
What, this is shit, I have better.
Jump speed and allows auto jump.
Oh wait!
Climb walls, ability to swim.
Where I can run super fast.
Is this also super fast?
Yeah.
I want this, I think.
I need a flipper.
Okay, I don't have that.
Sailfish boots.
Frog...
Wait a minute.
I have this.
Do I not?
Didn't I make something like that?
Hold on now.
Wait.
Hold on, am I blind?
I totally made that.
Oh wait, is it on...
Oh, there it is!
Heck yeah!
Glad I figured that out real quick, otherwise I would have been searching for this forever.
Yeah, let's make it.
Let's frickin' make it!
Operate everything.
No, not here.
It's here.
Yeah!
Frog webbing!
Melee speed, increases follow resistance.
Jump speed and...
Okay, so auto jump.
Let me see what that's all about.
Oh, I wasn't able to do that before?
Wait a minute.
Why is it not auto jumping up the wall?
Isn't that the entire point of this why that would be nice?
I mean, this is pretty neat.
That's...
Honestly, that's kind of sick.
Not gonna lie, that's pretty damn cool.
I feel like I also jump higher, am I crazy?
I think a little bit.
I mean, fall resistance is kind of useless now that I have this right.
But it definitely adds a dimension there.
Dude, I have so much mobility now.
It's actually wild.
But this is also immaterial.
Let me ask Dylan about that.
Dylan?
Oh, frog gear!
Ability to swim, climb walls, jump speed, fall resistance...
It ain't easy being green.
Oh yeah, I definitely want that.
I need a flipper for that.
Heck yeah, man.
But for now, I'm putting this here.
In fact, let's do this so they stay.
I'm starting to have way too many items here that I regularly use.
And can't live without... Oh, let me open this.
Shocked oyster, let's eat it, because why not?
This goes in here.
The sonar potion?
Uh, detects!
I need to try that right now, because I don't know what the fuck that means!
Drink!
Hurry!
Come on!
We don't have much time.
We gotta go immediately.
Give me a water body.
There we go.
Now, put this...
Detects hooked fish, huh?
How?
But, uh... Okay, so it...
Oh!
I can just let it... Oh!
I can just sit here and chill, then.
I'll be like drinking coffee.
Ah, that's a flounder.
Don't want that shit.
Next!
Oyster I want!
Oh my!
That way, I also don't break as many lines!
No, no, no, don't do it, don't do it.
Just wait.
I'm too fast on the trigger there.
See, I don't want that either.
Nope.
Okay, I'm loving this potion.
This potion is amazing.
One of the best potions of the game.
I could probably write a python script that would just detect whether or not a crate has been seen here and then click the mouse.
But that would be cheating!
You can't do that.
Come on, give me more crates.
Nice.
I've been fishing all night, it's morning now.
I wonder if you get special items during the night when you fish in certain areas.
Oh wait, nothing happening!
Okay, we're back.
It broke!
Okay.
I mean, I'll take the oysters.
Yeah, I'll take that too.
See,
that's awesome.
Delete this, I don't want flounders.
Or rock lobsters.
Or I... Okay, I'll keep that actually.
Alright, let's move on.
I need to go pick up my gold.
Fuck off, fuck off.
Dude, doing this is actually kind of... Maybe it's better.
Yeah, I mean... Yeah it is?
Because this has travel time when it flies, right?
But if I do this, it's like instantly there.
Think about that for a second.
Are you thinking about it?
Think about it.
Look!
Definitely better.
Hey!
Can I also... No, okay, I need to sort of guide it around obstacles.
I can't summon the thing I control on the other side of a wall.
That would be a little too broken.
Man, where the fuck... I could've sworn there was a desert in this game.
I shit you not.
I feel like I've seen that before.
Buh-buh-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo.
La-la-la-la!
Look at the turtle flying!
We're on an adventure!
Okay, I died here.
There.
It's time to go straight down.
But where did I go straight down?
I like this song.
Ah!
I passed the...
I guess I have not gone straight down then.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no.
Where's my straight down?
Is it here?
Is this my straight down?
Equip this also.
Oh, it is.
Oh, my God.
I hit it perfectly.
This time, we're not going to die randomly here.
We need party lights.
Party lights.
Oh, look at this.
Totally works.
Okay.
Hold on.
We're not going to die here again.
Oh, wait.
Oh, okay.
So we can look like...
That's actually really cool.
That's such a cool effect.
Cool idea for a weapon.
Now, I guess there's nothing else to it, but dig.
This time, I'm not going to die.
Oh, and also, you know what?
Actually, I'm just going to use the Danger Sense potion before I open the next chest, because otherwise, it may be wasted.
Right?
Straight down.
Oh, also, we need to eat the potion here.
Come on.
Oh, wait.
I can guide it, of course.
See ya.
I need to drink the potion that will give me powers.
The power of the mining.
Where?
Where is it?
Sword.
Mining.
Oh, watch this now.
Watch this.
Oh!
Brother!
That is power that no man should have, but I have gained it.
Holy fuckamoly.
Give me air.
Oh, wait.
We're back here now.
Keep going.
There's something immensely satisfying about this right now.
Here, please.
Thank you.
I'm dying to something.
Also, I got to drain this water at some point.
Otherwise, I can't really fall the way I intend to fall.
Damn.
Frickin' look at me now, compared to the beginning of the game, huh?
Look at what I've achieved.
Look at what I'm able to do.
I may die here.
No, I'm not gonna die.
I'm not gonna die.
We're fine.
Please stop that.
Okay, so we gotta go here.
I just need to find... Here we go.
This is it.
My god, I took a lot of damages now.
All the water has been drained.
Let's keep going.
Also, am I still on the right?
I am.
Whoa, it's so dark in here.
Chest!
This is the time.
What am I taking damage from?
What's happening?
Oh, there's an enemy!
Oh my god, I'm so blind.
Danger sense potion.
Kinda need to heal also.
Drink?
Okay, so this is fine.
Magic mirror?
Cool.
I have one of those.
There.
Deposit all.
Remove some of this stuff.
I also kinda want this option on again.
Yeah.
Because otherwise, I waste potion time.
I can't have that.
Sure.
Let's see.
Gold, torches.
It's a material.
Actually, have I ever tried putting that inside of Dylan?
Spelunker?
I'll eat it.
Let's keep going.
Oh, this is exciting looking.
We get to see everything on the way down.
Keep going.
Oh, we've got lava now.
Gotta be careful.
This is so exciting.
Would you look at that?
Kill them all.
There we go.
I want to heal now.
Ten seconds.
Let's take a breather here.
Oh, I see a chest.
Let me actually get that.
Another... Another one.
Dead man sweater.
I mean... No.
Yeah.
I need that.
Oh, what's happening?
Why did I just take a million damage?
Oh, the boulder.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Goddamn.
Fuck.
I even had the potion to see it.
Oh, that's... Wait, do I still... No, okay.
Goddamn it.
It's happy turtle time, guys.
Don't forget that.
You know what?
It's a good thing we went back anyway, because our inventory is a mess.
It's time to click on buttons here.
That button in particular.
Also disable this again.
This stuff can go... You know what?
All these up here can be, you know, that also.
Okay, Dylan, real quick.
What about this magic mirror?
Right.
Oh, wait.
I did check this.
I remember this now.
I need a PDA.
How the fuck did... You know what I always thought was interesting?
I'm gonna tell you this while I walk.
But you know what's really crazy to me?
Laptops.
Think about it.
Think about the laptop.
Okay, are you thinking about it?
I think about this.
Someone went out into the woods.
Right?
They went out into the woods and collected stuff.
And they built a fucking laptop.
I will never understand how that is possible.
It's made out of stuff from the earth.
You know, you take this, you take some wood, you take some, I don't know, stone or whatever, gold.
You'll make it go through some kind of process, right?
And you have a laptop.
It's insane to me.
It's absolutely insane.
And that's what I was thinking.
That's it.
That's the end of that thought.
Why am I running so slow?
Hello?
Why am I not getting maximum speed here?
Okay, just needs to charge up a little bit.
Charge.
Let's not pass the point where I went down.
The good news is we're gonna get down quick.
Amazing.
Oh, wait, did I pass it?
I didn't.
Look how that looks.
Amazing.
Just straight down.
Now I know what I'm missing.
It's this.
Once you get used to this, it actually kind of feels bad to go back after that.
Here we go.
Straight down we go, boys.
Let me light it up on my way.
How is this not amazing?
Dang.
Oh, that's a chest right there.
I think I looted that already, though.
I did.
Did I loot this one?
I think I did that one, too.
Yeah, this is where I died.
I don't want to die again.
How did I die last time?
Oh, yeah, I died up here.
I died to the boulder.
Oh, wow.
It was a boulder and traps.
Look at this.
It's all lined.
Okay, you know what?
From now on, whenever there's a chest, check everything.
Check your surroundings.
It could all be a trap, and it often is.
Dude, I just thought I died.
I read this and was like, wait, what just happened?
But I clicked on this by accident.
That just confused the hell out of me.
For a brief moment there, I was in nowhere land in my mind.
Okay, is it time to just keep going down, though, with lava?
Oh, wait, this is the thing I want to try.
I didn't bring my... Ah, that's unfortunate.
I wanted to bring the water weapon that I have to see if I could use that to create obsidian.
Don't tell me I actually did not bring it.
That's so dumb of me if I didn't.
I could use this, actually.
Yeah, let's use that.
And then we keep going down.
Go!
We're not going to be as fast this time, but that's okay.
The good thing is we're getting obsidian out of this, and we actually need that.
Heck yeah.
We need this obsidian.
We're so painfully slow now.
Oh, it's because I don't have this on.
Ah, this there.
We need party lights.
What?
I thought I had plenty of air!
No.
Why am I so terrible at this game?
What is happening right now?
What is actually wrong with me?
Fuck.
Unreal.
I regret everything I've done.
But the good news is we have obsidian now, so maybe we can play around with some hellstone stuff.
Sword.
Wait, where's my hellstone stuff?
Wait, hold on.
Is it in here?
Man, I have a lot of shit.
Jesus.
Is this real?
I don't need that right now.
I guess it was a good thing to clean up my inventory anyway.
God damn it.
Oh well.
You want to put this in here.
Mining potion.
Oh, there it is.
I can make more.
Nice.
Now what else can I make with this?
You know what?
Let's try this.
The imp staff.
Hops.
And then we go up here.
We have two now.
That's actually pretty dope.
Hold on now.
Didn't I also have some other item that allowed me to have one more summon.
I feel like I saw this somewhere.
It could just be the table though, unless I'm remembering wrong.
I feel like there was some other item that I had somewhere that allowed me to have more than one.
Not this one.
Movement speed after taking damage.
Shark pup.
Hmm.
I'm pretty sure I saw that somewhere.
Oh, now I can bring this with me.
Bring this instead.
I want to try this to make Obsidian.
Okay.
No, don't put it... Oh, I should totally do this actually.
There we go.
That would be the smart thing to do.
The magic mirror.
We have three of them on us.
Why did I bring all those?
Bad idea.
Those up here, I guess.
The masturbate.
We can put it... I don't... Yeah, I do want to fish though.
I kind of sounds insane.
Wait, why is this here now?
Hello?
Didn't I just put you in here?
Water bucket can stay here now.
I don't want it.
These are good to have.
This one can stay here as well.
It takes up a lot of, you know, spots.
I have a 270 Hellstone.
I don't think I'm going to be running out of that any time soon.
Put it in.
This one, I feel like I can leave here as well.
Let's do this as well.
Dude, this is actually kind of neat.
There's no reason not to have these two follow me around, I guess, if I'm going into combat.
If I'm going into a battle, why would I not do this?
Right?
There's like no downside here.
None.
Okay, let's go.
And it's very dark.
I guess I could light my path.
Oh, they're shooting.
Yo, cool.
That's freaking awesome.
That is so amazing.
That is just so incredible.
I shoot too.
We all shoot.
Is it just me or is it way more dark than usual?
It's not usually this dark during the night, is it?
Wait.
Oh, I thought there was a tunnel through there.
Oh, that one shoots in all kinds of directions.
Oh, I'm running out of stuff.
Oh, I thought these were enemies.
They're my friends.
What do I have on?
I have the digging thing on.
That's okay.
We can keep that on for now.
The good thing about these summons here, they are going to protect me against the little pesky enemies that are just small and buzzing and everywhere.
God, I hate those, you know?
That's what they're going to do for me.
It's going to be confusing at some point with all the projectiles on screen.
Okay, here it is.
This time, let's not fuck up.
Uh, I got a zombie.
Why did I?
Hold on.
Are these banners getting better?
Because I got one at the 500th zombie.
Like, why does it keep giving me if they're just the same?
Like, maybe this one is better than the others.
But I don't know.
Here we go.
We are falling to the bottom of the world.
And I'm shooting anything that comes near me.
That chest I looted.
Hold on.
What was that?
What's this?
Honey block.
Hold on.
Honey.
Interesting.
And a life crystal as well.
I'll take it.
Give me all of this, honey.
Come here.
Thank you.
Keep falling.
Wait, what is this?
Why is it yellow?
Oh, I guess it kind of makes sense.
There's a... oh wait, I was about to say there's a bee there, but there's a hornet, so not really the same.
What's happening here?
Oh, what is that up there?
Oh, it's a chest.
Wait, is my inventory actually full already?
Holy crap.
I forgot to empty the rest here, by the way.
That's... I fucked that up.
Pause it.
Everything.
And I guess eat that one.
That's why.
Okay, hold on.
Any traps?
Oh, I'm so scared.
Scared of opening.
A boom stick.
Fires a spread of bullets, really?
Oh, I don't have any ammo.
All right.
Cool.
Throwing knives.
Boo.
I'll take the others.
Honey dispenser.
Hey.
All right.
A honey dispenser.
Why am I taking damage here?
What is hitting me?
Some small projectiles I'm not seeing, I guess.
Loving this weapon here.
Oh, what's that?
Coffee!
No way.
Halo Darkness, my old friend.
It's a consumable.
Honestly, I don't even know where I'm going.
I'm just sort of exploring right now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Look at that.
We found a little house.
What is that right there?
Oh.
The merchant.
Oh, shit.
There
we go.
Just kill these fools.
There we go.
Spillunker.
Let's do it.
Delete this.
Delete.
Actually,
Halo.
And delete these.
I'm taking this chest with me, though.
Thank you.
Statue of a hornet.
We don't want that.
I can go to hell.
I can't stop digging.
Guys, I can't stop exploring.
Why is this so addicting?
I just want to go random directions, kill random enemies, get random loot.
You know what I feel?
I was about to say, you know what I'm saying and you know how I feel?
And it sort of became... What is that?
Oh, a gold pouch.
Cool.
Just five gold lying around.
That's awesome.
I do kind of want to zoom out and zoom back in.
Let's go up here.
Do I have my thingies with me?
My specialized thingies.
Oh, my inventory is...
It's very full.
Quick stack, deposit all, delete this, drink the coffee and drink the coffee in the glass too.
It's kind of cold at this point, but that's okay.
I don't mind.
Nice.
I have my... What is this again?
Topaz.
Neat.
Chest.
I'm getting that.
Let's be on the lookout for traps.
There we go.
I'm scared.
Okay, we're fine.
An angry lava charm.
Provide seven seconds of immunity to lava.
Hey, that's for you guys.
Gesters, archery, glow sticks and gold.
Thank you.
Gonna have lots of things to show to Dylan later.
What's this here?
This looks a little trappy to me.
Maybe not.
Sapphire's.
Oh, yeah.
I shall take it.
I should also take this.
Dude, my little imps or whatever are doing amazing work here.
One of the life crystals sell for good money.
Jungle torch.
Oh, we've got lava.
This is the time.
Get ready.
Um, where is it now?
There.
Oh, it doesn't work.
Oh, no.
Too bad.
Bring that.
Help these guys out, please.
Actually, what is going on over there?
That's kind of things going on here.
What's up, people?
Oh, my God, what a massacre.
Incredible.
Medusa statue.
Man, my inventory is full.
Holy shit.
Ah, okay.
Let's delete some things.
Delete this.
Delete that.
Don't delete that, of course.
Mud block.
Honestly.
No, it's going to get stacked up anyway.
Doesn't matter.
Silt is... Get rid of this.
What's damaging me?
Am I poisoned?
I kind of want to see a Medusa.
Do we get to see a Medusa?
Happy little tree.
Quick Hermes boots.
Thank you.
Quick stack.
Is there anything else I can delete?
The hook, honestly, goes away.
The angry lava charm is something I can combine with other things, so I'm excited about that.
Honestly, okay, the paint... the tree, although, is nice.
The merchant, I also want to keep.
These seem like good ones.
Beautiful ones.
The rich mahogany chest, I'll keep as well.
Hornet banner can be placed here.
Because why not?
Why if I just summon this here?
I kind of want to try it.
I'm not gonna lie.
This maybe seems a little crazy.
No, but let's not.
Two of these chests now.
Nice.
Oh, I kind of like this design of having the pillars underneath.
I feel like I should do something similar at home.
Somewhere.
Emeralds.
Get rid of these, honestly.
Tungsten ore can also go away.
I have so much of it.
Hup!
Such an efficient weapon here.
Oh my god.
Look at how many enemies there are.
This is a huge ass room.
Okay, no trap, please.
Okay.
Jacket band of regeneration.
Another one of these.
Don't want that.
Or that.
I do want this.
Thank you.
Give me all the loot.
Man, I gotta go back.
I just don't have enough room for this.
This is travesty.
No, I need to clean up my inventory properly here.
This is even with the double I wonder if I could get a second money trap.
How did I even get this?
At some point it was just in my inventory or like in my chest even.
But I probably put it there by accident and then found it later, but I still don't understand how I got it.
Probably just picked it up randomly among all the other things you pick up.
Click this amazing button.
The rich mahogany bookcase, we have to put that down somewhere.
An absolute must.
Let's get rid of these chests.
Delete them.
The mahogany bookcase goes here.
It's very rich.
There we go.
The merchant there.
Actually, I feel like the merchant would be better suited.
Here.
There you go.
Seymour.
Let me see your shop.
You still sell the old same thing, huh?
Let me actually quickly check what everyone has.
Sparkle.
It never stops celebrating.
I mean, I kind of want to buy all this, but it's so expensive.
So I'll do it when I have a million gold.
Bubble wand.
Smoke bomb.
Okay.
This one time at fishing camp, lightning struck the lake.
Suddenly, all the fish floated up to the service for free.
That's a cool story, bro.
Tell it again.
In the forest, the slimes are kind of gross.
Slimefish are even more so.
I don't want to swim with slimes, so yank one out of the water for me.
Slimefish.
Sure thing, buddy.
Why are you here?
I made you a house in the thing.
You must cleanse the world of this crimson.
Oh yeah?
What's the status?
The robust can is 6% crimson.
It's the same as it's always been.
Does it matter?
Why would I need to do it?
Sure.
At some point, I'm going to make a whole garden only with this, like maybe a little greenhouse even, off to the side away from the main building here, where I just have planters everywhere.
We're talking 20 planters.
That's going to be great.
All right, Dylan, I have questions for you.
Tell me about this angry lava charm.
Right.
Oh!
Wait, I can actually... No, I don't have this.
Wait.
Oh, molten charm.
Grants immunity to fire blocks.
Seven seconds of immunity to lava.
The thing I don't understand here, does this activate when I touch something, then?
Or is it like a button I need to press?
I guess I'll find out, huh?
Molten skull rows.
Wait, obsidian...
immunity to... Okay.
Magma skull.
Oh, this is... Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I want to make an obsidian skull, then.
For show!
Let's just do it.
Tell me I have that.
Obsidian.
Oh, did I use it all last time?
I think I did.
I used it to make hellstone.
Hellstone bars.
Unfortunates.
The honey dispenser.
Let's try this.
It looks like a king chair or something.
Oh, wait.
Bad placement.
I need to put that somewhere else.
You know, maybe outside would make sense.
Put it there.
Wait, what did I just...
Oh, I'm turning off the campfire!
Right, okay.
Whoops.
Uh, here we go.
Are you kidding me?
Why would I do any of this?
A honey dresser?
Are you kidding me?
That's horrible.
Nobody wants that.
I mean, maybe someone wants that.
I don't know.
Tell me about these boots again.
I need... okay.
That's all I can do with that.
Tell me about honey.
Epimination.
Honey block.
Stinger.
Hive.
Bottled honey.
Oh, improves natural healing for a short time.
Now that I'm interested in.
Also, this is interesting to me as well.
But hold on.
Where is the bottled honey?
How can I make it?
I think I have that.
I think I also have that.
I don't have this.
Probably I can use it with a empty bottle.
Tell me about this again.
Bottled honey!
Requi... oh!
Requi... required objects, honey.
Uh... wait, like... oh, like this?
Hold on.
This has to be it.
Maybe I need to place the honey?
Like that?
Required objects, honey.
So I need an object that is just called a honey, not a honey block.
But how do I do that?
I mean, this is a honey dispenser.
This should be able to give me honey, I imagine.
Hold on, let me see this again.
Used for special crafting.
Okay, yeah.
So it will allow me to... yeah, it will allow me to do these things, of course.
Ah, man.
Yeah, I'm not so sure about this.
I think I need to find honey in a different state.
Out in the wild, somehow.
Yeah, that's what I think.
Oh, we have these chests also, too.
Let me do that.
So we have two of these now.
Let me do this, that, and then we start off like that.
We're gonna alternate like this up here.
Shadow Chet, this can go in here.
There.
All right.
Anyway, for now, I'm actually dying in real life.
I need to eat.
And I need to call it right now.
I have a long day ahead of me tomorrow.
Oh, man.
This game is so nice to get back into after all this time.
Five days I haven't played, man.
Oh, yeah.
That was nice.
I needed that.
I needed that shot of Terraria straight into the veins.
How's everybody doing, huh?
I see potatoes in the chat.
I like that.
You guys know me.
Also, once again, shout out to Crowwater for these amazing emojis here.
The demon emoji is amazing.
Quick, pretend you're doing homework.
Man, homework.
Oh, that's a concept I haven't thought about in a while.
Are you liking Terraria compared to Minecraft?
A lot.
The same, I think.
Two very different games, though.
I expected this to be much more similar at the beginning, but now it's actually very different.
Yeah.
But it's also kind of similar.
They each have different strengths and weaknesses, I would say.
Like in Minecraft, there's almost no music and it's a rarity to get music.
Here, there's too much music and it's rare to get no music.
Actually, you never get no music.
I wish there was a middle ground between the two, you know?
But they're both equally amazing in their own way, I guess.
I'm curious to see where this goes, though.
Terraria, that is.
Terraria relaps after a week.
Hope you get back on track to cold turkey.
Now, I'm gonna be playing this more now that I'm healthy, man.
I'm having too much fun.
Good stream, solid one out of one, binary.
Like it, Jen.
Definitely.
Potato.
Good stream.
Hey, Speed.
I haven't seen you before.
Welcome.
By the way, for the people watching right now, and you don't know, there's actually a Discord you can join.
And somehow people in there have created an absolutely amazing community.
Check it out.
It's awesome.
And now it's time for me to bounce on out of here.
You almost beat the old one's army.
That was close.
Yeah, I did actually, but I noticed the health bar at the end.
So I think there's a boss there and it's not gonna be as easy as that.
I'll take it though.
At some point, I'll do it.
If you could have one accessory in real life, what would you take?
Probably a deck of cards.
Yeah.
No way, a Discord?
That sounds kind of demon to me.
I fucking love how you guys have made a whole... I don't even know what to call it.
A thing around that video.
That one resonated with you guys, huh?
Very unexpectedly, man.
Oh man, just in time for the end.
I'm so sorry unit hashtag PHNTK hashtag one.
Next time you'll catch it live at the beginning.
I know it.
I wish I had the patience to play games fully blind.
I mean, it just takes a while, but it's... I think the payoff of figuring things out is really nice.
Tosten.
Tosten erts.
I'm guessing you're either Danish, Norwegian, or Swedish?
Oliver, is it true that all streams are pre-recorded and the only part you do live is chat interaction?
Yes.
I mean, no.
I mean, no, it's not true.
Definitely not true.
But actually, speaking of that, I was thinking, how would you guys feel about the videos that I put up?
I put them as premieres.
Because people can actually sit and chat while it's going like a live stream.
Is that something people want?
Is that even a thing anyone wants at all?
Or is it like completely nah?
Because I see nobody else doing it on YouTube and I think, okay, maybe people hate it.
My question is though, so during a premiere, when people chat in the chat, right?
Is that saved?
Or is that chat lost forever?
Because it could be pretty cool to have that chat saved on the side, you know, like YouTube does it on the side with live streams.
It just really doesn't matter.
Yeah, so after the premiere, it just becomes a video, right?
It is saved.
See, that would be pretty cool, I think, for future people when watching it to see how, if they want, of course, to look at the live chat during it.
Does it need to be moderated?
I don't think so, because...
I mean, that's a good question.
I don't know.
I mean, it's not hard coded into the video, of course, so nothing is like forever branded.
And I always have the option to delete messages after the fact, I think, or mods do.
Actually, I'm not sure about that.
Maybe.
Sometimes the quality of premieres are worse than when the full video goes up.
Is that just because people are not letting it sit and process long enough on YouTube before the premiere hits?
What I'm asking is, is it just a skill issue for other YouTubers that they know they need to let it sit and process before actually letting it premiere?
Or is it actually worse quality overall?
Is that a thing?
Hey, Talona Rose.
You as well.
Thank you so much.
It's a skill issue.
How far through the game do you think you've gotten?
Cornflake?
007?
Um, hmm.
I mean, I've traversed the entire surface.
I've gotten all the way to the bottom.
So I want to say maybe 75%.
But don't tell me, of course.
Don't even confirm or deny.
Don't even react to that.
In fact, I think that beckons some spoilers, maybe, inadvertent spoilers.
So I'm just gonna bounce now.
Guys, thank you for watching.
This has been a great time once again.
I'll see you guys in the next Terraria stream, okay?
Join the Discord, have fun, like the video, jump up and down, and do three push-ups.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.